// pittsburghSteelers.ts

import { Topic } from '.';

export const pittsburghSteelers: Topic = {
  topic: 'Pittsburgh Steelers',
  level: 'Intermediate',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 100,
  totalTime: 600,
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Who is the all-time leading passer in Pittsburgh Steelers history?",
      choices: [
        "Ben Roethlisberger",
        "Terry Bradshaw",
        "Kordell Stewart",
        "Neil O’Donnell",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ben Roethlisberger"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Which year did the Pittsburgh Steelers win their first Super Bowl?",
      choices: ["1974", "1976", "1979", "1980"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["1974"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Who holds the record for the most career interceptions as a Pittsburgh Steeler?",
      choices: ["Mel Blount", "Troy Polamalu", "Rod Woodson", "Jack Butler"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mel Blount"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the Pittsburgh Steelers' home stadium?",
      choices: ["Heinz Field", "PNC Park", "Three Rivers Stadium", "Forbes Field"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Heinz Field"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the Pittsburgh Steelers’ all-time leading rusher?",
      choices: ["Franco Harris", "Jerome Bettis", "Willie Parker", "Le’Veon Bell"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Franco Harris"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Which coach led the Pittsburgh Steelers to four Super Bowl victories in the 1970s?",
      choices: ["Chuck Noll", "Bill Cowher", "Mike Tomlin", "Buddy Parker"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Chuck Noll"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is known as the “Steel Curtain” and was a dominant member of the Steelers’ defense in the 1970s?",
      choices: ["Joe Greene", "Jack Ham", "Andy Russell", "L.C. Greenwood"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Joe Greene"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Which Pittsburgh Steelers quarterback won two Super Bowl MVP awards?",
      choices: ["Terry Bradshaw", "Ben Roethlisberger", "Kordell Stewart", "Neil O’Donnell"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Terry Bradshaw"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "In which year did the Pittsburgh Steelers win their most recent Super Bowl?",
      choices: ["2005", "2008", "2010", "2013"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2008"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the official mascot of the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
      choices: ["Steely McBeam", "Steelie", "Iron Man", "Steel Panther"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Steely McBeam"],
      score: 10,
    },
  ],
};
